[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Yin Sign associated with the Fire Element.  People born under that sign are genuinely nice people.", "correct_answer": "Goat", "incorrect_answers": ["Monkey", "Tiger", "Rat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unique feature do the the fingers of the koala possess?", "correct_answer": "They have fingerprints.", "incorrect_answers": ["There are six fingers on each leg.", "All of these", "Each finger consist of 10 bones."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are all bears omnivores?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "William Conrad played Nero Wolfe and Frank Cannon - two detectives of unique proportions.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first self service grocery store?", "correct_answer": "Piggly Wiggly", "incorrect_answers": ["Safeway", "Atlantic  Pacific Tea Company", "Hinky Dinky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which medical specialty largely replaced the old general practice specialty?", "correct_answer": "Family Practice", "incorrect_answers": ["Internal Medicine", "General Surgery", "Obstetrics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film The World Is Not Enough, M is held captive in which tower in Istanbul?", "correct_answer": "Maiden Tower", "incorrect_answers": ["Sura Tower", "Haschish Tower", "Janissaries Tower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the 3rd largest city in Germany and the capital of its largest state, Bavaria.", "correct_answer": "Munich", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamburg", "Nuremberg", "Berlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This island, on which the volcano Etna is situated, is the largest Mediterranean island.", "correct_answer": "Sicily", "incorrect_answers": ["Corsica", "Rhodes", "Sardinia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In medical parlance, what is an AKA?", "correct_answer": "The removal of a limb", "incorrect_answers": ["An alcoholic", "An antibiotic", "A patient"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sloths have this number of toes and fingers depending on the family they belong to.", "correct_answer": "Two or three", "incorrect_answers": ["Sloths do not have toes.", "Four or five", "One or two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Erythrocytes are a type of blood cells, consisting mainly of hemoglobin. What does the word erythro mean?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Knowledge", "Cell", "White"]}]